fwpolice.com 2017-05-14

# Privacy Policy – FWPolice

### Browser Collected Information

When you visit the the Fireworks Police web site, we may store some or all of the following: the Internet address from which you access the web site (IP), date and time, the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to our site, the name of the file or words you searched, items clicked on a page, and the browser and operating system used. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site and identify system performance or problem areas. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of the site, to analyze patterns of usage, and to make the site more useful. However, this information is not used for associating search terms or patterns of site navigation with individual users. The Fireworks Police periodically deletes its Web logs. On occasion, the Fireworks Police may provide this information to third party entities it contracts with for the purposes of research analysis.

### Personal Information

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an email, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with information or material that you request. If provided, personally identifiable information is maintained in a database that is regularly purged. Third party contractors may have access to this information in order to provide an initial response to your question or comment. These contractors are held to strict policies to safeguard the information and provide the same level of privacy protection as guaranteed by HEOP.org. On occasion, we may conduct a study concerning the types of questions sent to us. These studies help us to improve our Web sites in order to make them more responsive to the needs of our users.

To prevent problems from occurring in the future, please do note that any information that is sent via this e-mail form or posted on our site becomes property of the Fireworks Police. With this being said, we reserve full rights to forward, publish and transfer your message to any of our sponsors. Furthermore, the Fireworks Police reserves full rights to publish your submitted entry in the the Fireworks Police Guestbook, F.A.Q., and/or any other section of this site.

### Reliability of Information

The Fireworks Police is a private organization dedicated in providing information, resources and tutorials for the Adobe Fireworks software. Any information we provide is provided as-is with no warranty  With this being said, if any false information is provided by any of our representatives, we are not held responsible. The Fireworks Police staff and representatives search the World Wide Web and contacts sponsors to request information that may be helpful. However, as stated above, we cannot guarantee that the provided information is 100% correct.

### Cookies

A “cookie” is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk allowing our server to “remember” specific information about your session. While visiting certain sites on the Fireworks Police server (maintained by [Fleech Media](http://fleech.com/ "Fleech Media") and [E10Host](http://e10host.com/ "E10Host")), you may occasionally encounter a Web page that employs cookies to make it easier to use the dynamic features of these Web pages. The cookie and the information about your session will be destroyed automatically shortly after you close your browser. However, the cookies are not permanently stored on your computer. You can set your browser to disable cookies or prompt you before a cookie is accepted. If you do not want to receive cookies, you will still be able to use the Fireworks Police and documents, but will be unable to use cookie-dependent features. In exceptional circumstances persistent cookies may be employed, but they are never used for tracking users’ queries or navigation through the site.

### Links to Other Sites

Some pages on our site provide links to other Internet sites that provide further information on a topic. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row]
